Okay, I'll start by looking for bold.
حسنًا، سأبدأ بالبحث عن أي كلمة بخط غامق.
To do that I will hit Cmd+F and then search for bold.
للقيام بذلك، سأضغط على Cmd+F ثم أبحث عن كلمة بخط غامق.
Now this brings me to a bold faced element called &lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;
ينقلني هذا الآن إلى عنصر مكتوب بخط غامق يسمى &lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;
That looks pretty reasonable, but
ويبدو ذلك معقولًا للغاية
it may be hard to see there is a second search result.
ولكن ربما يصعب رؤية وجود نتيجة بحث ثانية.
So I'm going hit enter again. And that brings me to the strong element.
لذا سأضغط على إدخال مرة أخرى. وينقلني ذلك إلى العنصر strong.
Now the strong element is something that has importance and
والآن يمثل العنصر strong شيئًا ما ذي أهمية
is typically displayed in bold.
ويُعرض عادة بالخط الغامق.
In fact I recommend using strong.
في الواقع، أوصي باستخدام العنصر strong.
Let me show you how that looks.
دعوني أريكم كيف يبدو ذلك.
So I've gone ahead and wrapped the text with a strong tag and
حسنًا لقد تابعت ووضعت علامة العنصر strong حول النص
as I said the b would be fine too if you did that.
وكما قلت، ستكون علامة b مناسبة أيضًا إذا فعلتم ذلك.
And then I've saved it and I will come over to the browser and hit refresh and
وبعد ذلك، حفظتها وانتقلت إلى المتصفح وضغطت على تحديث
then wallah the text is bold.
ثم ظهر النص مكتوبًا بخط غامق.
Okay next up.
حسنًا، التالي.
I need to make this text emphasized.
أحتاج إلى تأكيد هذا النص.
Back inside the Mozilla developer network I'm going to search for
وبالرجوع إلى Mozilla developer network، سأبحث عن
emphasis.
كلمة emphasis.
There we go. And that quickly takes me to
ها نحن. وينقلني ذلك سريعًا
the em element which you saw before.
إلى عنصر em الذي رأيتموه من قبل.
The element marks that something has a lot of importance and
ويشير العنصر إلى أن شيء ما ذو أهمية كبيرة
so that looks good to me.
لذا يبدو هذا جيدًا بالنسبة لي.
You'll also note that right underneath it you'll have something called i.
ستلاحظون أيضًا وجود شيء ما بعده مباشرة يسمى i.
I will make something italic incidentally.
ويعني أنني سأكتب شيء ما بأحرف مائلة.
But you actually aren't supposed to use the  element for any itallics.
ولكن في الواقع لا يُفترض أن تستخدموا العنصر لأي أحرف مائلة.
It actually has a different purpose now which you can read about here.
يُستخدم حقًا لغرض آخر يمكن أن تقرؤوا عنه هنا الآن.
Let me show you how the element looks.
دعوني أريكم كيف يبدو العنصر.
So, i've added the opening tag and the closing tag.
حسنًا، لقد أضفت علامة افتتاحية وعلامة إغلاق.
Around This content.
حول هذا المحتوى.
And then I'll come over to the browser and hit refresh.
وبعد ذلك، سأنتقل إلى المتصفح وأضغط على تحديث.
And there you go.
وها نحن ذا.
This text is now emphasized.
تم التأكيد على هذا النص الآن.
Incidentally, in the next lesson you'll be learning another way
وبالمناسبة ستتعرفون في الدرس التالي على طريقة أخرى
of making text bold and italics.
لكتابة النص بأحرف غامقة ومائلة.
I hope you remember that there are many ways to accomplish a lot of tasks
أتمنى أن تتذكروا أن هناك العديد من الطرق لإنجاز العديد من المهام
inside the browser.
داخل المتصفح.